<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed
  xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
  xmlns:thr="http://purl.org/syndication/thread/1.0"
  xml:lang="en-US"
  xml:base="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/wp-atom.php"
   >
	<title type="text">The Steinbrenner High School Oracle</title>
	<subtitle type="text">Steinbrenner High School&#039;s Official News Magazine</subtitle>

	<updated>2013-10-18T17:00:23Z</updated>

	<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com" />
	<id>http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/feed/atom/</id>
	<link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/feed/atom/" />

	<generator uri="http://wordpress.org/" version="3.6.1">WordPress</generator>
		<entry>
		<author>
			<name>EmmaS</name>
					</author>
		<title type="html"><![CDATA[Swim falls to Plant in season&#8217;s conclusion]]></title>
		<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/18/unable-claim-win-final-meet-season/" />
		<id>http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/?p=8117</id>
		<updated>2013-10-18T17:00:23Z</updated>
		<published>2013-10-18T16:57:48Z</published>
		<category scheme="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com" term="Sports" /><category scheme="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com" term="Swimming" />		<summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Steinbrenner swim team competed against the county champions Plant High School for their final meet of the season Thursday. The Steinbrenner girls finishing with a score of 56 to 127 and boys finishing with 82 points and Plant with 103, for both teams their second loss of the year. [&#8230;]]]></summary>
		<content type="html" xml:base="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/18/unable-claim-win-final-meet-season/"><![CDATA[<p>The Steinbrenner swim team competed against the county champions Plant High School for their final meet of the season Thursday. The Steinbrenner girls finishing with a score of 56 to 127 and boys finishing with 82 points and Plant with 103, for both teams their second loss of the year.</p>
<p>Steinbrenner&#8217;s game plan was to try and get as many second and third combinations as they could. If they were able to get those two slots, the points they would acquire would be in their favor, but out of the 24 events Steinbrenner only had five races where they placed second and third.</p>
<p>“We gave it all we got and I am proud to have had my boys push,” said boys senior captain, Austin Childers, who swam in the 100 butterfly, back stoke and 400 free relay. Childers is hoping to move past district and move on to Regionals with five other boys.</p>
<p>Both the boys and girls teams will finish 5-2 this year after the lose Thursday. The other meets the team lost other then Plant were the boys losing to King in the first meet of the season and the girls losing to Sickles.</p>
<p>The only time Steinbrenner swim has topped Plant was last year at Western Conference, when the boys were able to pull off the upset of the powerful Panthers.</p>
<p>“It was kind of expected. It’s Plant, but we ended on a great note,” says girls senior captain, Taylor Sohlberg. Sohlberg raced in the 500 free style coming in fifth with a time of 6:36.27, and is hoping to swim the race again at districts.</p>
<p>Even though Steinbrenner swim suffered the loss in their final meet of the season, they have districts to look forward to on October 29.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Emma Stevens / Staff Writer</strong></p>
]]></content>
		<link rel="replies" type="text/html" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/18/unable-claim-win-final-meet-season/#comments" thr:count="0"/>
		<link rel="replies" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/18/unable-claim-win-final-meet-season/feed/atom/" thr:count="0"/>
		<thr:total>0</thr:total>
	</entry>
		<entry>
		<author>
			<name>AlexT</name>
					</author>
		<title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Magic and Boy Parts; &#8216;Coven&#8217; loses some suspense [S3E2]]]></title>
		<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/17/ahs-episode-2/" />
		<id>http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/?p=8105</id>
		<updated>2013-10-17T15:57:44Z</updated>
		<published>2013-10-17T15:57:09Z</published>
		<category scheme="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com" term="&#039;AHS&#039;" /><category scheme="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com" term="Arts/Entertainment" /><category scheme="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com" term="TV" />		<summary type="html"><![CDATA[As much as I wanted episode two of Coven to breeze past the infamous sophomore slump, it dabbled in the realm of mediocrity. One could claim that there was much action in this episode, but nothing followed through; it was mostly just exposition. Conversations were dry and were deprived of good [&#8230;]]]></summary>
		<content type="html" xml:base="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/17/ahs-episode-2/"><![CDATA[<p>As much as I wanted episode two of <i>Coven </i>to breeze past the infamous sophomore slump, it dabbled in the realm of mediocrity. One could claim that there was much action in this episode, but nothing followed through; it was mostly just exposition. Conversations were dry and were deprived of good character and Emma Roberts&#8217;s laughable acting did not help the story arch at all.</p>
<p>The one thing I loved about the first episode of the season was that it set the overall tone very well with it&#8217;s rich narration and storytelling. The episode was filled with amazing dialogue that made audiences fall in love with our favorite actors all over again, but tonight&#8217;s episode lacked this pizzazz.</p>
<p>It began like a late night crime thriller with previously dead witch Misty Day resurrecting two hunters&#8217; alligator kills and forcing the reptiles to eat the hunters alive. The scene had some great special effects but I feel it was mostly done as a quick scare, making it no better than lame modern big budget horror films that just say &#8220;Boo!&#8221; the entire time. <em>American Horror Story</em>&#8216;s fan-base isn&#8217;t composed of people who want jump scares; they enjoy eerie suspenseful situations with much build up and a large climax.</p>
<div id="attachment_8112" class="wp-caption alignright" style="width: 310px"><a href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/American-Horror-Story-Coven-Jessica-Lange-Kathy-Bates.png"><img class="size-medium wp-image-8112" alt="Fiona Goode, Marie LaLaurie and Marie Laveau are dominant characters in 'Coven', wrestling over the secret to immortality and providing climactic plot twists." src="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/American-Horror-Story-Coven-Jessica-Lange-Kathy-Bates-300x153.png" width="300" height="153" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Fiona Goode, Marie LaLaurie and Marie Laveau are dominant characters in &#8216;Coven&#8217;, wrestling over the secret to immortality and providing climactic plot twists.</p></div>
<p>The main draw of last night&#8217;s program was the resurrection of everyone&#8217;s favorite frat brother Kyle Spencer (Evan Peters) after movie star witch Madison Montgomery flipped the party bus he rode in. Our two main characters waltzed right into a secured morgue facility with the explanation that movie star Madison Montgomery had previously learned how to break locks after shooting for a movie about a cat burglar. They then pieced together different parts of the fraternity brothers to make one perfectly featured gory boyfriend whom they then resurrected with a spell that Madison stole from the headmistress of their witchcraft school. Emma Roberts awkwardly repeated the words from the spell to the audience with strobe lights and smoke machines firing behind her. The girls drew a satanic pentagram on their new creation&#8217;s body and pledged to the underworld to bring back the soul of Kyle Spencer. All while this was happening, my face contorted into a quite displeased form as I was unsure if I was watching <em>American Horror Story</em> or if my hand had accidentally hit the remote and I was actually watching weird local programming.</p>
<p>The one thing I did like about this episode was the infertility battle that headmistress Cordelia Foxx faced with her husband. Early in the episode they visited a doctor who told them that it was unlikely for them to naturally conceive a child and Foxx&#8217;s husband suggested they use witchcraft to help increase their chances of conception, a thought originally denied by Cordelia as it dabbled in dark magic which she never wanted to touch. Nevertheless, later in the episode, she formed some sort of ritualistic circle with snake eggs and charcoal galore where she and her husband &#8220;made magic&#8221; and most likely finally conceived their future child.</p>
<p>Moving to the uneventful dialogue I was speaking of was Fiona Good&#8217;s conversation with the powerful voodoo queen Marie Laveau (Angela Bassett) who possess the fateful key to immortality, the secret which Fiona so wishes to uncover. We find out in their conversation that she and Fiona&#8217;s ancestors have been colliding for centuries now and the fact that Fiona wants something of Laveau&#8217;s is quite scandalous.   The conversation &#8220;ends&#8221; with a snide remark from Fiona Good&#8217;s actor Azura Skye as she walks out the door of Laveau&#8217;s hair salon leaving the conversation open for the next time they meet.</p>
<p>Maybe I am being a bit eager with my story progression, but I am not one to leave multiple stories, even small ones, busted wide open so that later they can be picked up. I am reminded a lot of one of my favorite TV shows <em>LOST,</em> which was so ambitious in the beginning that they left so many things open at the end, and I hope <em>Coven</em> doesn&#8217;t fall into the same void of untwisted ends just like that show did. <strong>7.5/10</strong></p>
<p><strong>Alex Troutt/Senior Staff Writer</strong></p>
]]></content>
		<link rel="replies" type="text/html" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/17/ahs-episode-2/#comments" thr:count="0"/>
		<link rel="replies" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/17/ahs-episode-2/feed/atom/" thr:count="0"/>
		<thr:total>0</thr:total>
	</entry>
		<entry>
		<author>
			<name>EmilyG</name>
					</author>
		<title type="html"><![CDATA[Contracted to a bright future [STAFF EDITORIAL]]]></title>
		<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/15/contracted-bright-future/" />
		<id>http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/?p=8099</id>
		<updated>2013-10-15T15:47:17Z</updated>
		<published>2013-10-15T15:45:56Z</published>
		<category scheme="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com" term="Opinion" /><category scheme="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com" term="Staff Editorials" />		<summary type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Placement (AP) classes are classes designed to challenge students, to provide an example of a college course, and to aid the college preparation process. Every February during course selection week, students strive to pack their schedule with AP classes; and often times end up taking more than they can [&#8230;]]]></summary>
		<content type="html" xml:base="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/15/contracted-bright-future/"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/apcontract.jpg"><img class="alignright size-medium wp-image-8100" alt="apcontract" src="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/apcontract-300x233.jpg" width="300" height="233" /></a>Advanced Placement (AP) classes are classes designed to challenge students, to provide an example of a college course, and to aid the college preparation process. Every February during course selection week, students strive to pack their schedule with AP classes; and often times end up taking more than they can handle.<br />
In order to reduce the amount of students that feel overwhelmed by their schedule, guidance counselors take certain measures like requiring teacher recommendations for every AP and Honors class and sending home “AP contracts” that essentially bind a student to a class.<br />
Senior Alex Simmons is currently enrolled in six AP classes and feels as though the AP contract is a good representation of the college future AP classes are trying to prepare students for.<br />
“I agree with it because AP classes are college level classes, you won’t be able to change your professor if you don’t like them, so I don’t think it should be changed,” said Simmons.<br />
When students attempt to drop AP classes during the first few weeks of school, they fail to realize the mass effect it has on the entire master schedule.<br />
“It’s all about the master schedule and the contract with the teachers that we have to let them know before the transfer period that this is what you’re going to be teaching next year. Because if they don’t like their schedule they might want to go to another school for different jobs, it’s more about the big picture not just the individual class itself,” said guidance department head Susanne Powell.<br />
The guidance department tries their best to handle each student’s situation individually and case by case, but the problem lies in the warnings the guidance department attempts to push when kids are signing up for the difficult classes.<br />
The AP contract, teacher recommendations, and the stress they put on the difficulty of the AP classes are put in place to reduce student desires to drop their AP classes. These tactics are not made to be taken lightly, and students who do so do not deserve to drop their classes.<br />
AP classes are formulated to be difficult and challenge a student, if a student does not feel as though they can handle the work load, they should have been responsible enough to look at the consequences before they signed up for the class.<br />
The high school purpose is to prepare students for the academic college life that is looming in the future. In college, students have a designated period to drop or add classes, and the decision is final after that. The student at that age is expected to take on the responsibility of a difficult schedule, and their high school preparation is a reflection of that.<br />
High school students should start becoming aware of the work load AP classes demand and recognize the fact that no matter the AP class (even if it considered “easy”) will force the student to study and spend a considerable amount of time dedicated to the subject.<br />
By dropping AP classes because a student is overwhelmed, they are essentially saying they did not take into account the precautionary planning and the words of the guidance counselors into consideration.<br />
Admittedly, the system isn’t perfect. To give a student a more accurate view of an AP class, guidance counselors could consider letting a potential AP student “shadow” a class and sit in the class during their lunch period.<br />
Guidance counselors could possibly make it a requirement to have a student talk to a teacher about an AP class difficulty level and give the students a “grace” period to drop a class.<br />
“I want everyone to be happy with their schedule, but it’s not a perfect world, so you’ll probably never have the perfect schedule and the perfect teacher, and nothing everything is going to be perfect,” said Powell.<br />
The utopian idea of a “perfect schedule” will always been in sights for high school students, but for now they should realize the consequences that come with an AP class and think a little more before they pack their schedule with APs to boost their GPA or prove that they can handle the workload.</p>
<p><strong>Sam Bequer / Editor in Chief</strong></p>
]]></content>
		<link rel="replies" type="text/html" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/15/contracted-bright-future/#comments" thr:count="0"/>
		<link rel="replies" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/15/contracted-bright-future/feed/atom/" thr:count="0"/>
		<thr:total>0</thr:total>
	</entry>
		<entry>
		<author>
			<name>EmilyG</name>
					</author>
		<title type="html"><![CDATA[Going for the leap year]]></title>
		<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/15/leap-year/" />
		<id>http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/?p=8095</id>
		<updated>2013-10-15T15:47:37Z</updated>
		<published>2013-10-15T15:44:34Z</published>
		<category scheme="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com" term="Opinion" />		<summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fulfilling aspirations and dreams is something most students, who practically spend their lives stuck in school, strive to achieve. Fortunately this includes the option of leaving school early, going straight through to college after graduation, or simply awaiting whatever fate has in store for them. Though taking a year off [&#8230;]]]></summary>
		<content type="html" xml:base="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/15/leap-year/"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/taking-a-year-off.jpg"><img class="alignright size-medium wp-image-8097" alt="taking a year off" src="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/taking-a-year-off-300x300.jpg" width="300" height="300" /></a>Fulfilling aspirations and dreams is something most students, who practically spend their lives stuck in school, strive to achieve.<br />
Fortunately this includes the option of leaving school early, going straight through to college after graduation, or simply awaiting whatever fate has in store for them. Though taking a year off of high school is not generally suggested or common, it’s still an applicable choice that can be made.<br />
Ever since I was little, I grew a strong passion for the University of Michigan. A detailed memory got engraved in my mind when my uncle and I would spend tireless nights on vacation playing NCAA football on his Xbox 360. Although I did grow an adoration for the Division 1 athletic school, my parents made it clear that without a scholarship, I could not, would not, and should not by any means get my hopes up for post high school classes out of state. Then again, can anyone truly stop a stubborn teenager once they’ve set their mind?<br />
According to an article on U.S. News Weekly, the topped ranked colleges in the nation are up North. Therefore, it gives students living in the lower states a disadvantage when it comes to choosing in-state colleges. But what makes sense to me is if a student plans on paying tons of money for tuition, they might as well attend a school they love.<br />
The question is this: Is it worth taking the year off of school to become a resident of a new state and even start your life off with a job and settle down before picking your education back up?<br />
Disadvantages in taking a year off include losing the motivation of actually wanting to go to college and study after the year is up, becoming unfocused in forms of getting a job and not being able to keep up with school therefore not attending at all. Some people can balance their priorities, but the lower class usually can’t afford it.<br />
Around 60% of high school graduates choose to attend four-year colleges every year, while others choose technical schools and two-year community colleges.<br />
Usually students who can’t afford any means of education after high school end up enrolling into the military. According to a Policymic article, three million young Americans drop out of high school every year, and over 8,000 per day.<br />
On the other hand, taking a year off allows you to study at the college of your dreams, and that’s all that can be said. All that is needed to make this happen (which is easier said than done) is moving to the state that the particular school is, or moving in with any family you have available, for a year.<br />
On average, about 71% of American students graduate high school each year. Applying and getting into the school is a completely different story. Hopefully you are sure whether or not you have what it takes to get into the college or university, but if not a scholarship is always there to rely on.</p>
<p><strong>Ricardo Morales / Graphics Dept.</strong></p>
]]></content>
		<link rel="replies" type="text/html" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/15/leap-year/#comments" thr:count="0"/>
		<link rel="replies" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/15/leap-year/feed/atom/" thr:count="0"/>
		<thr:total>0</thr:total>
	</entry>
		<entry>
		<author>
			<name>NatalyC</name>
					</author>
		<title type="html"><![CDATA[Dreams In Production: Music Production Club Showcases Student Talents]]></title>
		<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/15/dreams-production-music-production-club-showcases-student-talents/" />
		<id>http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/?p=8089</id>
		<updated>2013-10-15T15:43:37Z</updated>
		<published>2013-10-15T15:43:37Z</published>
		<category scheme="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com" term="Arts/Entertainment" /><category scheme="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com" term="News" />		<summary type="html"><![CDATA[“When you do what you love, you never work a day in your life.” For most proclaimed talents at Steinbrenner High school with dreams of one day fulfilling aspirations and becoming well known (or for many, just known at all), this simply worded quote is but a life moral. The [&#8230;]]]></summary>
		<content type="html" xml:base="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/15/dreams-production-music-production-club-showcases-student-talents/"><![CDATA[<p>“When you do what you love, you never work a day in your life.”</p>
<p>For most proclaimed talents at Steinbrenner High school with dreams of one day fulfilling aspirations and becoming well known (or for many, just known at all), this simply worded quote is but a life moral. The music production club, sponsored by ceramics teacher Don Sizemore and founded by a few passionate students, is being offered for those students who want to learn or already love producing music.</p>
<div id="attachment_8092" class="wp-caption alignright" style="width: 235px"><a href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/Natal2y.jpg"><img class="size-medium wp-image-8092" alt="Music Production Club members Steven Lewis (left) and Matthew Geier (right). With the help of Don Sizemore, both students started the club." src="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/Natal2y-225x300.jpg" width="225" height="300" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Music Production Club members Steven Lewis (left) and Matthew Geier (right). With the help of Don Sizemore, both students started the club.</p></div>
<p>For Sizemore, being a young musician and performing with an alternative band helped him grasp the passion for this field and led him to build a soundproof recording studio in his house. He was highly supportive in starting the club, claiming that it definitely had the potential to go far. “Mr. Wolf had a student in his class approach him, yet knew that I played music and sent the student to me to figure out what I could do for them,” said Sizemore. To any student, it’s always unexpected to find a teacher that seeks the same interests as them, and this club offers the opportunity to work alongside Sizemore and some already experienced peers (Matthew Geier, Steven Lewis, Samuel Pachon), and programs made for recording musical “works of art”.</p>
<p>“It’ll expand to each generation and find something new within the club, knowledge to knowledge,” said Geier, in hopes that the legacy of music production club will live on.</p>
<p>Music is one of, if not the, most competitive fields in the real world. Computer recording programs run anywhere from $90 to $500. This particular club would issue Reaper; a free recording program used by most amateurs on the rise in attempts to perfect what they have come to love and want others to hear.<br />
“[This club] is a melting pot for kids who want to make music or learn how to in an open environment and become the best producer,” said Lewis. Lewis also specified that “Learning is key” and Pachon described the club as “an outlet for people who come from all walks of life”.</p>
<p>Club dues are still to be determined, and most equipment if not all will be supplied. Whoever has access to a computer or an interest in the music producing field is welcome. Be sure to meet with Matthew Geier, Samuel Pachon, or Steven Lewis if interested in entering the Music Production Club.</p>
<p>They meet on gold club days, and you can visit room 201 for more information.</p>
<p><strong>Ricardo Morales/Graphics Department</strong></p>
]]></content>
		<link rel="replies" type="text/html" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/15/dreams-production-music-production-club-showcases-student-talents/#comments" thr:count="0"/>
		<link rel="replies" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/15/dreams-production-music-production-club-showcases-student-talents/feed/atom/" thr:count="0"/>
		<thr:total>0</thr:total>
	</entry>
		<entry>
		<author>
			<name>EmilyG</name>
					</author>
		<title type="html"><![CDATA[Anything he can use, she can use better [SATIRE]]]></title>
		<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/15/use-satire/" />
		<id>http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/?p=8091</id>
		<updated>2013-10-15T15:47:56Z</updated>
		<published>2013-10-15T15:42:46Z</published>
		<category scheme="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com" term="Opinion" />		<summary type="html"><![CDATA[As many people have noticed, the world around us is changing rapidly. Men and women can no longer use the same things. For example, Bic’s “For Her” pens have recently hit stores. These feminine pens have helped women all over the country write even better than before. “I’m so excited,” [&#8230;]]]></summary>
		<content type="html" xml:base="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/15/use-satire/"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/BOY-PEN-CONFUSION.jpg"><img class="alignright size-medium wp-image-8093" alt="BOY PEN CONFUSION" src="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/BOY-PEN-CONFUSION-300x300.jpg" width="300" height="300" /></a>As many people have noticed, the world around us is changing rapidly. Men and women can no longer use the same things. For example, Bic’s “For Her” pens have recently hit stores. These feminine pens have helped women all over the country write even better than before.<br />
“I’m so excited,” said author Mary Book. “I had so much trouble holding those man pens. The “For Her” pens are much better and easier to write with.”<br />
The “For Her” pens have caused a trend all over the country. Charmin toilet paper recently released toilet paper for women.<br />
“It really has been a blessing for all us women,” said frequent toilet user Gotta Go. “I used to be stuck on the toilet for hours and now everything is real quick.”<br />
Go is one of many women who have suffered at the hands of men’s toilet paper. Recent studies report women who have been stuck on the toilet for numerous days at a time. Where did all the women go? Well, they were stuck in the bathroom, until this papyrus miracle.<br />
Following the lead of Bic and Charmin, Publix grocery stores have decided to have a men and women’s side of the store, with specific foods on each side.<br />
“Separate but equal is what I always say,” said Publix store manager, Tom Foody.<br />
With all the attention that women are getting, some men are very angered by the special treatment that women are receiving.<br />
“It’s very annoying actually,” said Thomas Mann. “Why must men get all the generic stuff? We’re people too.”<br />
Mann is especially angry about the Oneida forks for women. These special utensils are designed specifically for delicate female hands.<br />
“Sometimes when I’m really hungry, all I can find are my wife’s forks,” said Mann. “Most of the time I end up eating with my hands.”<br />
Oneida is currently working on knives for women too.<br />
“We don’t want women’s delicate hands being cut by our sharp, manly knives,” said Oneida CEO, Silver Ware. “Our new knives will be much more comfortable and user friendly for women. To let you in on a little secret &#8211; we’re working on women’s spoons too.”<br />
The knives are expected to be released sometime in November and the spoons sometime in December 2014.<br />
We also have word that in mid January, women will be blessed with their very own toilets. Pink and all! No more will girls have to run around doing the potty dance when they can have their very own porcelain throne right in the comfort of their own home. Out with those boyish toilets and in with the new.<br />
Women and men have been forced to use the same things. Now, companies all around the world are starting to realize that women can’t use the same general products because their needs far exceed those of any man.</p>
<p><strong>Sophie Bocksnick / Staff Writer</strong></p>
]]></content>
		<link rel="replies" type="text/html" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/15/use-satire/#comments" thr:count="0"/>
		<link rel="replies" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/15/use-satire/feed/atom/" thr:count="0"/>
		<thr:total>0</thr:total>
	</entry>
		<entry>
		<author>
			<name>Evan Abramson</name>
					</author>
		<title type="html"><![CDATA[Despite homecoming spirit, warriors come up short in second half, lose to wharton]]></title>
		<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/13/homecoming-spirit-warriors-short-half-lose-wharton/" />
		<id>http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/?p=8066</id>
		<updated>2013-10-13T21:54:58Z</updated>
		<published>2013-10-13T21:54:58Z</published>
		<category scheme="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com" term="Football" /><category scheme="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com" term="Sports" />		<summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lutz&#8211; The Warriors (1-5) were outlasted Friday night in a 45-28 losing effort to the Wharton Wildcats (6-1). “It’s a big boy’s schedule we are playing right now and it’s tough” said Warriors head coach Andres Perez. Senior quarterback, Curtis Fitch’s 240 passing yards and two passing touchdowns just weren’t [&#8230;]]]></summary>
		<content type="html" xml:base="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/13/homecoming-spirit-warriors-short-half-lose-wharton/"><![CDATA[<div id="attachment_8076" class="wp-caption alignright" style="width: 310px"><a href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/DSC_0129.jpg"><img class="size-medium wp-image-8076" title="Emma Stevens / Oracle" alt="Emma Stevens / Oracle" src="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/DSC_0129-300x200.jpg" width="300" height="200" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Grant Wilson returns his interception of Wharton quarterback Chase Litton in the third quarter. The Warriors had two interceptions on the night.</p></div>
<p>Lutz&#8211; The Warriors (1-5) were outlasted Friday night in a 45-28 losing effort to the Wharton Wildcats (6-1).</p>
<p>“It’s a big boy’s schedule we are playing right now and it’s tough” said Warriors head coach Andres Perez.</p>
<p>Senior quarterback, Curtis Fitch’s 240 passing yards and two passing touchdowns just weren’t enough to get his team over the hump. The Steinbrenner offense stalled out in the second half, after going score for score with the Wildcats all the way up to 28 points a piece.</p>
<p>“We just failed to capitalize on those scoring opportunities,” said Perez, “We had over 300 yards total offense and that’s always a good thing to see but we just need to keep on improving on our execution”</p>
<p>After giving up 600 offensive yards to Wharton Friday night (480 passing yards to Wildcat quarterback, Chase Litton), the Warriors defense will try and get back into their dominating grove in the upcoming matchup against district rival, Wiregrass Ranch (3-3) on the road.</p>
<p>“Bottom line, we have to focus now on these three next district games and if you know anything about high school football, they are the most important aspect of any teams focus. It’s been our goal and still is our goal to win these remaining games” said Perez.</p>
<p><strong> Evan Abramson / Senior Staff Writer</strong></p>
]]></content>
		<link rel="replies" type="text/html" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/13/homecoming-spirit-warriors-short-half-lose-wharton/#comments" thr:count="0"/>
		<link rel="replies" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/13/homecoming-spirit-warriors-short-half-lose-wharton/feed/atom/" thr:count="0"/>
		<thr:total>0</thr:total>
	</entry>
		<entry>
		<author>
			<name>NatalyC</name>
					</author>
		<title type="html"><![CDATA[&#8216;American Horror Story: Coven&#8217; hits the bull&#8217;s eye S3 E1 [Review]]]></title>
		<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/10/american-horror-story-s3-e1/" />
		<id>http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/?p=8038</id>
		<updated>2013-10-11T01:42:28Z</updated>
		<published>2013-10-11T01:36:27Z</published>
		<category scheme="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com" term="&#039;AHS&#039;" /><category scheme="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com" term="Arts/Entertainment" /><category scheme="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com" term="TV" />		<summary type="html"><![CDATA[Warning: This television program is intended for mature audiences and should not be watched alone or in complete darkness for the sake of your own mental health. A boarding school for witches may sound like the beginning of a tacky teen novel, but American Horror Story: Coven can of course [&#8230;]]]></summary>
		<content type="html" xml:base="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/10/american-horror-story-s3-e1/"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Warning: This television program is intended for mature audiences and should not be watched alone or in complete darkness for the sake of your own mental health.</strong></p>
<p>A boarding school for witches may sound like the beginning of a tacky teen novel, but <em>American Horror Story: Coven</em> can of course pull it off and scare us senseless while they&#8217;re at it. Just  in time for Halloween, Season 3 kicks off with Zoe Benson (Taissa Farmiga) who accidentally murders her boyfriend (praying mantis style) and then finds out she&#8217;s a witch. Her parents ship her to a boarding school where she meets human voodoo doll Queenie (Gabourey Sidibe), movie star Madison Montgomery (Emma Roberts), and young medium Nan (Jamie Brewer). Sarah Paulson is casted as headmistress Cordelia Foxx, and Jessica Lange appears later as Fiona Good, an older woman obsessed with maintaining her youth.</p>
<div id="attachment_8061" class="wp-caption alignright" style="width: 253px"><a href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/FX_AHS_ImageGallery_0000_031.jpg"><img class="size-medium wp-image-8061" alt="'American Horror Story: Coven' finally returned October 9th with an interesting season premiere that set hopes high for next week." src="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/FX_AHS_ImageGallery_0000_031-243x300.jpg" width="243" height="300" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">&#8216;American Horror Story: Coven&#8217; finally returned October 9th with an interesting season premiere that sets hopes high for next week.</p></div>
<p>Along with her movie star friend, Zoe attends a college party where she meets frat boy Kyle Spencer (Evan Peters). Fans rejoice at the reunion of their favorite couple, though the happiness is short-lived. Montgomery is drugged and gang-raped, and as Kyle runs after the others to try and retrieve the video they&#8217;d taken, Montgomery flips their bus. She kills all but two of the fraternity brothers, neither of which is Kyle.</p>
<p>Perhaps the scariest scenes in <em>Coven</em> involved Madame LaLaurie (Kathy Bates), a character based on serial killer Delphine LaLaurie, who would torture black slaves in her underground chamber. LaLaurie dies after being poisoned by a woman seeking revenge for her husband, but later on in the episode she is brought back by Fiona Good, though we aren&#8217;t exactly told how. The opening credits too contributed to the show&#8217;s scary factor (with the creepy-sounding intro music and flashing images) along with the gore and usual suspenseful moments.</p>
<p>Though it&#8217;s highly unlikely that producers would snatch Evan Peters away so quickly, I admit I felt a twinge of panic at his death. Maybe they&#8217;re planning to once more bring Peters back as a ghost (only Season 1 kids remember), or Zoe will beg her witch friends to help put him back together. He will undoubtedly reappear; fans would go berserk otherwise.</p>
<p>The rest of the episode was beautifully crafted in terms of showing what was to come as producers wrap it up with Zoe&#8217;s murder of the surviving frat boy that raped Madison. Fiona also mysteriously revives Madame LaLaurie, and this is what might lead viewers to believe that Kyle is likely to return as well.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s beyond me how producers (Murphy and Falchuk) manage to think up so many clever ways to leave an impression. <em>Coven</em> sets high expectations from only the first episode; it&#8217;s looking much better than <em>Asylum</em>, which was so wrought with gore that it overshadowed the plot. I&#8217;m grateful for the break from psychotic forest cannibals and evil nuns; thankfully, the best and the brightest have been brought back for season 3 (though I&#8217;m still iffy about Emma Roberts), and once more Jessica Lange and Taissa Farmiga earn leading roles. <em>Coven</em> is a different and more appreciated type of scary, as it leaves the door wide open for anything to wander in.<strong> Score: 9.5/10.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Nataly Capote/A&amp;E Editor</strong></p>
]]></content>
		<link rel="replies" type="text/html" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/10/american-horror-story-s3-e1/#comments" thr:count="0"/>
		<link rel="replies" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/10/american-horror-story-s3-e1/feed/atom/" thr:count="0"/>
		<thr:total>0</thr:total>
	</entry>
		<entry>
		<author>
			<name>Evan Abramson</name>
					</author>
		<title type="html"><![CDATA[Warriors suffer another tough loss, this time in district play]]></title>
		<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/10/warriors-suffer-tough-loss-time-district-play/" />
		<id>http://oraclenewspaper.com/?p=8017</id>
		<updated>2013-10-10T17:08:42Z</updated>
		<published>2013-10-10T17:08:42Z</published>
		<category scheme="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com" term="Football" /><category scheme="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com" term="Sports" />		<summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lutz&#8211; The Steinbrenner Warriors (1-4) gave up 54 points to district rival, Tampa Bay Tech (5-1) while only putting up 28. Up until the start of the third quarter, the Warrior underdogs put up a fight thanks to newly utilized offensive weapon, junior flex player, Kezio Snelling. Snelling, who has [&#8230;]]]></summary>
		<content type="html" xml:base="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/10/warriors-suffer-tough-loss-time-district-play/"><![CDATA[<div id="attachment_8051" class="wp-caption alignright" style="width: 310px"><a href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/DSC_0119.jpg"><img class="size-medium wp-image-8051" title="Emma Stevens / Oracle" alt="DSC_0119" src="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/DSC_0119-300x200.jpg" width="300" height="200" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Center Brian Ford prepares to snap the ball. Steinbrenner&#8217;s 28 points was the second highest it has scored all season.</p></div>
<p>Lutz&#8211; The Steinbrenner Warriors (1-4) gave up 54 points to district rival, Tampa Bay Tech (5-1) while only putting up 28.</p>
<p>Up until the start of the third quarter, the Warrior underdogs put up a fight thanks to newly utilized offensive weapon, junior flex player, Kezio Snelling. Snelling, who has been the main return man for the Warriors, was able to put Steinbrenner on the board in the first ten minutes of play with back to back kickoff return touchdowns of 92 yards.</p>
<p>“Bottom line, we thought special teams wise, we can do something special on kickoff returns. Our blocking and our front lines were picking early and that’s the benefit of our guys working their butts off” said Perez.</p>
<p>“Yeah I scored, but it doesn’t mean anything if we don’t win” said Snelling.</p>
<p>The Warrior running game was not able to get started. Instead, senior quarterback, Curtis Fitch, coming off 210 passing yards at Sickles, threw for approximately 140 yards on 14 completed passes out of 31 attempts. He was able to find Snelling for a touchdown with an 11-yard pass with 8:17 left of the third quarter, that tied the game. Snelling ended the night just under 200 yards with a total of 195.</p>
<p>Senior Jake Carroll, coming back from an injury that took him out of the Warriors lineup for several weeks, was forced to play out wide as a wide receiver option for Fitch, since the running game wasn’t working. Carroll had 59 yards on 3 receptions along with a fumble.</p>
<p>“Bottom line, we have to execute better. That’s the key” said Perez.</p>
<p>The Warriors will go on to play the Wharton Wildcats (5-1) on the 11<sup>th</sup> at home at 7:30 PM.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Evan Abramson / Senior Staff Writer</p>
]]></content>
		<link rel="replies" type="text/html" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/10/warriors-suffer-tough-loss-time-district-play/#comments" thr:count="0"/>
		<link rel="replies" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/10/warriors-suffer-tough-loss-time-district-play/feed/atom/" thr:count="0"/>
		<thr:total>0</thr:total>
	</entry>
		<entry>
		<author>
			<name>NatalyC</name>
					</author>
		<title type="html"><![CDATA[Miley Gone Wild; ‘Bangerz’ Triumphs As Surprise Success]]></title>
		<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/05/miley-wild-bangerz-surprise-success/" />
		<id>http://oraclenewspaper.com/?p=8004</id>
		<updated>2013-10-06T03:07:58Z</updated>
		<published>2013-10-06T02:50:17Z</published>
		<category scheme="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com" term="Arts/Entertainment" /><category scheme="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com" term="Music" />		<summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before I begin, I have to admit that I was one of those people who, back in 2008, couldn’t stand Miley Cyrus or her blonde alter-ego. It’s strange how now that she’s gathered all of the world’s attention&#8211;and gone completely crazy&#8211;she manages to produce an album worth some recognition. We’ve [&#8230;]]]></summary>
		<content type="html" xml:base="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/05/miley-wild-bangerz-surprise-success/"><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Before I begin, I have to admit that I was one of those people who, back in 2008, couldn’t stand Miley Cyrus or her blonde alter-ego. It’s strange how now that she’s gathered all of the world’s attention&#8211;and gone completely crazy&#8211;she manages to produce an album worth some recognition.</p>
<p dir="ltr">We’ve heard “We Can’t Stop” and “Wrecking Ball” enough times, so they’re hardly worth talking about. I simply have to mention that I judged these tracks so harshly because Miley’s mental breakdown took me by surprise, and the music videos were, to be honest, openly awful. But the songs themselves, I later realized, are catchy, cleverly put together, and show an entirely different side of this “American sweetheart” we thought we knew.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The rest of <em>Bangerz </em>comes as a bit of a shock; “Adore You” is a slow-moving, artistic combination of instrumentals (cellos accompany the leisurely computerized beat in the background) with Cyrus’s voice synthed to match the pace of the song. Perhaps inspired by the current EDM rage, Cyrus impresses with this track, as well as with “4&#215;4”, which, despite its strange lyrics (“Driving so fast ‘bout to piss on myself”), still manages to stand as a decent track and shows her country girl side. Later we see that Cyrus and Britney Spears have more in common than their liking to chopping off all of their hair; their voices blend nicely on “SMS” and turn them into a powerful pop duo.</p>
<p dir="ltr">“Stand By Me” gives an interesting twist on the song title which we know has been done and re-done endlessly. Cyrus inserts her own vibe into it, changes the lyrics around, and pairs with American rapper Future to create a distinct, enigmatic sound. “Get It Right” is less hard-hitting  and “Drive” is similar to “Adore You” in its melody and lyrics, though the latter is significantly better.</p>
<div id="attachment_8008" class="wp-caption alignright" style="width: 310px"><a href="http://oraclenewspaper.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/20130911193705Miley_Cyrus_Bangerz_Album_Cover.jpg"><img class="size-medium wp-image-8008" alt="Cyrus released Bangerz this Friday, October 4th, and collaborated with several rappers that changed up her sound." src="http://oraclenewspaper.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/20130911193705Miley_Cyrus_Bangerz_Album_Cover-300x300.jpg" width="300" height="300" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Cyrus released her fourth LP this past Friday, October 4th, and collaborated with several rappers that changed up her sound.</p></div>
<p dir="ltr">On “Maybe You’re Right” Cyrus (possibly) sings of a recent breakup while proving her vocal range abilities, and here I was thinking she was tone-deaf. “FU” is one of the strongest tracks on <em>Bangerz</em>, and stands as a perfect example of Cyrus’s monumental improvement as an artist. Her collaboration with French Montana makes it all the better, as he picks up the mic when Cyrus needs a break from her passionate lyric-belting. “Someone Else” is another great track that, without the deep bass synths and impressively catchy chorus, would’ve blended into the background of this album.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The only thing I saw a real problem with was “Love Money Party”, as it was just another obnoxious “I’m a party animal” type of song and was basically just Miley telling us what she does on her weekends. Apart from this, this album is an amazing outburst from Cyrus (compare it to “Hoedown Throwdown” if you don’t believe me) and exemplifies her growth as an artist and a young adult in the music industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">My theory is that this was her plan all along; to wait until she could let herself go and prove to everyone what she could really do (in terms of producing music). She’s tired of being the good girl, and even if the only way she can prove herself as a serious artist is to go completely nuts, I respect her intentions. I do have to tell you this: don’t watch the music videos to these songs, because you’ll hate them. Simply listen to them and you’ll know exactly what I mean. There is no way we can expect Cyrus, now 20 years old, to stay Hannah Montana forever. It was only a matter of time before the wig came off&#8211;this time for good. <strong>Score: 8.5/10.</strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">Strongest tracks: &#8220;Adore You&#8221;, &#8220;FU&#8221;, &#8220;Someone Else&#8221;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Weakest tracks: &#8220;Love Money Party&#8221;, &#8220;Rooting For My Baby&#8221;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Nataly Capote/A&amp;E Editor</strong></p>
]]></content>
		<link rel="replies" type="text/html" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/05/miley-wild-bangerz-surprise-success/#comments" thr:count="6"/>
		<link rel="replies" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/05/miley-wild-bangerz-surprise-success/feed/atom/" thr:count="6"/>
		<thr:total>6</thr:total>
	</entry>
		<entry>
		<author>
			<name>NatalyC</name>
					</author>
		<title type="html"><![CDATA[Panic! At The Disco: A band &#8216;too rare to die&#8217;]]></title>
		<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/03/panic-band-too-rare-die/" />
		<id>http://oraclenewspaper.com/?p=7990</id>
		<updated>2013-10-06T03:13:14Z</updated>
		<published>2013-10-03T15:36:28Z</published>
		<category scheme="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com" term="Arts/Entertainment" /><category scheme="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com" term="Music" />		<summary type="html"><![CDATA[There isn’t a soul who doesn’t recognize “I Write Sins Not Tragedies” as Panic! At The Disco’s pride and joy, and doesn&#8217;t admit that this is one of the best alternative rock songs out there. It was released back in 2006, when Panic!’s fame was at its peak. We haven’t [&#8230;]]]></summary>
		<content type="html" xml:base="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/03/panic-band-too-rare-die/"><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">There isn’t a soul who doesn’t recognize “I Write Sins Not Tragedies” as Panic! At The Disco’s pride and joy, and doesn&#8217;t admit that this is one of the best alternative rock songs out there. It was released back in 2006, when Panic!’s fame was at its peak. We haven’t heard of them since 2011 (<em>Vices &amp; Virtues</em>), so it was a surprise when they released “Miss Jackson” this summer, a surprisingly good single for a band that was thought to have lost its popularity.<em> Too Weird to Live, Too Rare to Die</em> is another side of Panic!, a more electronic twist to their alternative rock.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Because there is the tendency to release an album’s best track before the album itself, “Miss Jackson” stands well above the rest of <em>Too Weird</em>, with it’s swinging rock and roll chants based off of Janet Jackson’s “Nasty” (1986). It’s clearly the fan (and radio) favorite, though this doesn’t mean the rest of the album isn’t worth a listen. An electric vibe infiltrates “This Is Gospel”, the album’s opener, during which I would’ve preferred to hear the raw talent of Brandon Urie’s voice rather than the autotune they mixed into the song, though I feel better during the chorus when things pick up. “Vegas Lights” is a fun party track, “Nicotine” holds its own, and “Girls/Girls/Boys” is upbeat, though a bit colorless at times. They’re solid mid-album tracks more telling of Panic!’s new style.</p>
<div id="attachment_7992" class="wp-caption alignright" style="width: 310px"><a href="http://oraclenewspaper.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/pngbase64d6f60bd9de233922.png"><img class="size-medium wp-image-7992" alt="Panic! At The Disco's album will be released on October 8th, though it's available to stream through their website." src="http://oraclenewspaper.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/pngbase64d6f60bd9de233922-300x300.png" width="300" height="300" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Panic! At The Disco&#8217;s album will be released on October 8th, though it&#8217;s available to stream through their website.</p></div>
<p dir="ltr">“Casual Affair” has a haunting yet irresistible electric melody that makes it stand out as one of <em>Too Weird</em>’s top tracks; you can still hear  the drums pumping in your head long after you’ve turned it off. “Far Too Young To Die” and “Collar Full” are just as clever, (I’ve got a collar full of chemistry from your company/So maybe tonight I’ll be the libertine) and sound like something you’d listen to on a late-night drive through the city. In 15 lines of lyric, “At The End of All Things” manages to convey a plethora of emotion with the piano and violin instrumentals we hear in the background. Though I’d much prefer to hear an acoustic version of this song, I still feel the love-sickness in every second, and it makes for a beautiful finish to the album.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With <em>Too Weird</em>, Panic! strays from their old style&#8211;their style being weird, lengthily titled songs that were still somehow ingenious (But let&#8217;s be honest, did &#8220;There’s a Good Reason These Tables Are Numbered Honey, You Just Haven’t Thought of It Yet&#8221; have to have <em>that</em> long of a song title?). <em>Too Weird</em> , ironically enough, is too <em>normal</em> for a band like Panic!, but they manage to pull it off, even if some songs sound a bit M83. Some people who previously didn’t like Panic! might even consider them now, because this band has evolved along with the music industry and their new sound is more hard-hitting and electronic. Some fans might miss the quirkiness from <em>Pretty. Odd.</em> or <em>A Fever You Can’t Sweat Out</em>, but these days are well behind them for a reason.</p>
<p>The ten tracks on this album (and the album’s title) are enough to say exactly what this band intended: as weird as they are, they aren’t planning to die out any time soon. Panic! holds too much talent to disappear from the music industry and they’re a once-in-a-lifetime combination of skills. On<em> Too Weird,</em> Panic! shows their strengths along with their superb orchestration and Urie’s uncanny vocal abilities. <strong>Score: 8/10.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Nataly Capote/A&amp;E Editor</strong></p>
]]></content>
		<link rel="replies" type="text/html" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/03/panic-band-too-rare-die/#comments" thr:count="1"/>
		<link rel="replies" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/03/panic-band-too-rare-die/feed/atom/" thr:count="1"/>
		<thr:total>1</thr:total>
	</entry>
		<entry>
		<author>
			<name>NatalyC</name>
					</author>
		<title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Timberlake strikes again with “The 20/20 Experience &#8211; Part 2 of 2”]]></title>
		<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/03/justin-timberlake-strikes-the-2020-experience-part-2-2/" />
		<id>http://oraclenewspaper.com/?p=7982</id>
		<updated>2013-10-03T10:33:18Z</updated>
		<published>2013-10-03T10:33:18Z</published>
		<category scheme="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com" term="Arts/Entertainment" /><category scheme="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com" term="Music" />		<summary type="html"><![CDATA[I find it incredibly challenging to be unbiased towards Justin Timberlake’s new album, The 20/20 Experience Part 2 of 2, mostly because of Timberlake’s domination of the music industry and his huge success with previous albums. 20/20 Part 1 took everyone by surprise back in March due to its wide [&#8230;]]]></summary>
		<content type="html" xml:base="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/03/justin-timberlake-strikes-the-2020-experience-part-2-2/"><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">I find it incredibly challenging to be unbiased towards Justin Timberlake’s new album, <em>The 20/20 Experience Part 2 of 2</em>, mostly because of Timberlake’s domination of the music industry and his huge success with previous albums. <em>20/20</em> <em>Part 1</em> took everyone by surprise back in March due to its wide range of musical diversity and lengthy tracks lasting up to seven minutes. <em>Part 2</em> is, in my opinion, one of the most outstanding albums to be released this year. To be honest, I didn’t think that Timberlake would be able to top his first album. I mean, how much music can you release in bulk before it becomes repetitive and just pushes the envelope? I was proved wrong as soon as I listened to the first track. If I could summarize this album in the easiest way possible, I would tell you to imagine the love-child of <em>Justified</em> and <em>FutureSex/LoveSounds</em>.</p>
<div id="attachment_7994" class="wp-caption alignright" style="width: 310px"><a href="http://oraclenewspaper.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/20-20-experience-2-timberlake.jpg"><img class="size-medium wp-image-7994" alt="'20/20 Part 2' released September 30th, and proved to be just as revolutionary as 'Part 1'." src="http://oraclenewspaper.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/20-20-experience-2-timberlake-300x300.jpg" width="300" height="300" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">&#8217;20/20 Part 2&#8242; released September 30th, and proved to be just as revolutionary as &#8216;Part 1&#8242;.</p></div>
<p dir="ltr">The album’s opener is “Gimme What I Don’t Know (I Want)”, a very <em>Justified</em> infused sound with beatboxing, overlapping voices, and a noticeable key change halfway through the song. There’s something about this song that seems as if it were meant to be on <em>Part 1</em> of <em>20/20</em> and it just didn’t make the cut. That being said, the lyrics and background instrumentals are simple and repetitive, turning this into a song you most likely won’t be putting on repeat. “True Blood” falls along these guidelines as well; while listening to this song, I couldn’t help but actually burst into uncontrollable laughter. This track almost makes me feel as though Timberlake sat down in his studio and said to himself, “You know, because this album is coming out near October, I should make a Halloween themed song,” when in reality this song is just 10 minutes of uncomfortable.</p>
<p dir="ltr">There are two collaboration tracks on this album, and in “Murder” Justin Timberlake joins forces with Jay-Z once again to produce a catchy masterpiece. Jay-Z and Timberlake turn out to be a very odd but powerful combination. Not only are the two touring together, but every single that they release together become instant hits (“Suit &amp; Tie”, “Holy Grail”). The second collaboration was something that I’m surprised took this long to happen: Timberlake and Drake. These men, known for their powerful lyrics towards the opposite sex, came together to produce one of the most sexual songs I’ve heard in a long time, “Cabaret”. With a title such as that, and knowing the past lyrical styles of Timberlake and Drake, I knew how I’d feel about this track. While listening, take the time to notice not just the amazing instrumentals, but the words. This song is filled with hidden innuendos and double meaning phrases that will make you blush.</p>
<p>This album wouldn’t be complete with the already chart topping hit singles “Take Back the Night” and “TKO”. Because these tracks were released to the radio, the edited versions cut out practically half of the “TKO”’s seven minutes. The last two minutes of it are, in my opinion, the best part of the entire song. The song breaks down from it’s strong instrumentals into nothing but Timberlake’s beatboxing followed by a subtle beat to support it, showcasing just how talented Timberlake is. As for “Take Back the Night”, this song relates very closely to the style of Michael Jackson, which is exactly what Timberlake intended. You don’t have to be a genius to understand that Timberlake is clearly stating that he is the new “King of Pop”. Although, to be completely honest, that statement may not be far from the truth.  <strong>Score: 9/10</strong></p>
<p><strong>Gabby Shusterman/Photo Editor</strong></p>
]]></content>
		<link rel="replies" type="text/html" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/03/justin-timberlake-strikes-the-2020-experience-part-2-2/#comments" thr:count="0"/>
		<link rel="replies" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://www.oraclenewspaper.com/2013/10/03/justin-timberlake-strikes-the-2020-experience-part-2-2/feed/atom/" thr:count="0"/>
		<thr:total>0</thr:total>
	</entry>
	</feed>
